micros.com 2014-12-17

# Oracle | MICROS | Privacy Policy

MICROS Systems has been [acquired](http://www.oracle.com/us/corporate/acquisitions/micros/index.html) by Oracle and will soon transition to the Oracle Privacy Policy. Click [here](http://www.oracle.com/us/legal/privacy/privacy-policy/index.html) to view the Oracle Privacy Policy and read your options for opt out and compliance issues under that policy. Please note that the provisions of MICROS Systems’ Privacy Policy below will remain active until the policy transition is complete.

MICROS Systems, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our current information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.micros.com.

**Information Collected and Use of Information**

  * When you request information on products or register on MICROS Web properties, we may require you to provide your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and relevant information about the size and type of your business. 
  * In certain areas of www.micros.com, visitors will also be given a choice to be included on MICROS mailing lists. If you are included on MICROS's mailing list(s), we may notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. Our site uses a registration form for users to request information on our products and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). Contact information from the registration form is used to send information about our company and promotional material to our customers. The contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings [see the choice/opt-out section below]. 
  * We also track the referring URL of our users to provide statistical information regarding the effectiveness of our site and marketing programs. 

**Automatically Collected Data**

This website uses Google Analytics, a Web analysis service of Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies ‒ text files that are stored on your computer and that enable an analysis of your use of the website. The information about your use of this website, which is generated by the cookie, is usually sent to a Google server in the USA and stored there. By order of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to analyze your use of the website, to compile reports about the website activities and to render other services related to the use of the website and of the Internet in general to the website operator. The IP addresses sent by your browser within the scope of Google Analytics will not be consolidated with other data of Google. You can prevent the storage of cookies by configuring your browser software accordingly; in this case, however, you may not be able to use all functions of this website. Moreover, you can prevent the collection of data concerning your use of the website (including your IP address), which are generated by the cookie, and the processing of these data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in that is available under the following link: [download and install the browser plug-in](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

**Onward Transfer**

Except as may be required by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with applicable law or with legal process served on MICROS Systems, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MICROS Systems, Inc., or this site, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MICROS Systems, Inc., the site, or the public, MICROS presently does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any registration or inquiry. The information that we collect is used solely to better understand visitors' use of MICROS's site and to conduct user-requested follow-up activities. 

**Use of "cookies"**

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a Web site can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow Web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor's individual preferences. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major Web sites use them. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use www.micros.com. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it as you navigate through the member areas, however, we do not store personal identifying information in cookies. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. User personal information is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have specific access rights to such systems. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database so as not to receive future communications. The company ordinarily will process the request within 30 days of receipt. MICROS will not process third party requests. 

  1. You can send email to [webeditor@micros.com](mailto:webeditor@micros.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  
 _7031 Columbia Gateway Drive, Columbia, MD 21046 Attn: Webmaster_

**Correct/Update**

This site provides users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. The company ordinarily will process the request within 30 days of receipt. MICROS will not process third party requests. 

  1. email [webeditor@micros.com](mailto:webeditor@micros.com)
  2. send mail to the following postal address:  
 _7031 Columbia Gateway Drive, Columbia, MD 21046 USA Attn: webmaster_

**Contacting the Web Site Administrator**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

_Webmaster_  
 _MICROS Systems, Inc._  
 _7031 Columbia Gateway Drive_  
 _Columbia MD 21046_  
USA  
(443) 285-6000 (tel) 

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. **www.micros.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Children's Privacy Protection**

MICROS abides by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requirements. www.micros.com does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 13, and does not knowingly collect data from children. When www.micros.com requests that a user enter personal data, MICROS does not inquire as to the age of the user. If MICROS discovers that it has personal data from a child under the age of 13 through its website, MICROS will eliminate that data from our systems. 

**Your consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide according to this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you can always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
